

Gabriele Glinni

Interpreter and translator with two years' experience in financial consulting. In 2022, I discovered a strong interest in programming and administrative management, which led me to further train with professionalizing courses. I am looking for a work environment where I can use my language, communication and computer skills and grow professionally. I am considered an employee of strong commitment and willpower, often referred to as a workaholic, capable of bringing remarkable results to the business reality.

PERSONAL INFO

Phone number: 3382558779 Email: gabrieleglinni@gmail.com Born in Rome, 29/01/1993 - 00137

Personal websites: LinkedIn • Github • Ascend-ent (e-

book) • Pillole di Folklore e Scrittura (blog)

HARD AND SOFT SKILLS

- Foreign languages: English: C1, Portuguese: C1,
 French: B1, Spanish: B1
- Programming: [General] Git, TDD, OOP,
 [Frontend] HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, [Backend]
 C#, Java, .NET, JavaScript, PHP, [Database]
 MySQL, [CMS] WordPress
- Professional knowledge of the Microsoft Office package: Word, PowerPoint, Excel
- Knowledge and counseling of SAP modules
- CAT Tools: SDL Trados Studio, MateCat
- **Subtitling software**: Aegisub, SubtitleWorkshop
- Computer graphic softwares: Canva, Adobe Photoshop
- · Organized use of CRMs such as Salesforce
- Writing techniques and SEO strategies
- · Leadership, KPI monitoring
- Empathy, teamwork, team motivation
- Storytelling, creative writing, article writing

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Administrative Clerk

Verdeco / December 2022 - Currently

 Documentary and cadastral verification of different clients, feasibility of paperwork, processing of financing, and constant contact with installers of environmentally sustainable systems.

Team Leader Financial Advisor

Risolvi il Tuo Debito / March 2021 - November 2022

- I analyze the debt situation of potential clients in order to subsequently provide a liquidation plan, retain them and "educate" them financially (CRIF, non-performing loans, aggredibility, etc.).
- As a Team Leader I also train and mentor new employees, motivate the team, analyze and monitor KPIs, and achieve high goals through use of Google Sheets. For consecutive months I have been recognized as the department employee with the highest productivity, winning a productivity award.

Freelance Translator

- I translated, from French and English, the subtitles of eight movies for the "Traduzione per il sottotitolaggio nell'ambito dei festival cinematografici internazionali" festival, for NAPIS SpA.
- I have revised in Italian and translated into English
 "Discovering the Science of Evil", an essay on Criminology by PhD Yuri Ciro Mennella.

EDUCATION AND STUDIES

GJordan di Gauss Jordan S.r.l

Professional Intensive SAP Training Course MM/FI Modules / January 2023 - March 2023

MM/FI Module Customization; Material Master Data
Management; Purchasing Process (RDA-ODA-EM); MM Invoice
(MIRO); Inventory Management; RDA/ODA Release Procedures;
Stock Analysis; MRP (RDA through MRP); ODA and CDC;
Service Provision; Chart of Accounts Management Simulation
creation of BBP "As-Is" and "To-Be" documents.

Archimede Informatica

Professionalizing course in Web programming and web design / October 2022 - July 2023

 Development of static and dynamic websites, curated in appearance, SEO and content, using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript and PHP languages.

UNINT - Università degli Studi Internazionali di Roma

Master's Degree in Interpreting and Translation / October 2017

- April 2020 (106/110)
 - Interpreting and Translation skills-legal, medical, literary, manual, wine; professional use of CAT Tools.

SSML Gregorio VII

I level Master's in Translation and Cinetelevision Adaptation / October 2016 - June 2017

Bachelor's Degree in Linguistic Mediation *I October 2012 - March 2016* (105/110)

 Interpreting skills (to and from language), Translation, Sociology, Linguistics; during the master's, skills in film-television adaptation and subtitling.

Autorizzo il trattamento dei miei dati personali presenti nel cv ai sensi dell'art. 13 del Decreto Legislativo 30 giugno 2003, n. 196 "Codice in materia di protezione dei dati personali" e dell'art. 13 del GDPR (Regolamento UE 2016/679).

Shryl